<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Mypalmike&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://mypalmike.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Mypalmike&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 10:20:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://mypalmike.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Peek6502</title>
      <link>http://mypalmike.github.io/posts/atari-800-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 10:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mypalmike.github.io/posts/atari-800-intro/</guid>
      <description>I recently started writing an emulator for the Atari 800 computer in the language Rust.
The Atari 800 was my first computer as a child. I had begged and pleaded with my parents to get me a computer after being shown how to write simple BASIC programs on my elementary school&#39;s Apple 2. My family was of moderate means, so buying something with a total cost of over $1000 was not something taken lightly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LibGDX, Preferences, and Android</title>
      <link>http://mypalmike.github.io/posts/libgdx-prefs-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 09:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mypalmike.github.io/posts/libgdx-prefs-android/</guid>
      <description>Another day of coding with LibGDX, another annoying Android issue.
This time, it involves a Preferences object. I have a settings menu where the user can adjust things like sound effects volume, etc. There is a single Preferences object that lasts the entire lifetime of the game. In the settings menu, I read from and write to this object. And obviously I read the values elsewhere for the settings to take effect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixing sound effects issues in LibGDX on Android</title>
      <link>http://mypalmike.github.io/posts/libgdx-sfx-issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 22:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mypalmike.github.io/posts/libgdx-sfx-issues/</guid>
      <description>Just a forewarning: this is not a definitive explanation for everything that can go wrong with your sound effects in LibGDX - just some information I learned while debugging some issues I ran into. I still have more questions than answers.
Sound effects are often one of the last things you will implement in an independent game project. You&#39;ve got this nearly complete game that just needs some polish in the form of bleeps and bloops.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skastic: An image-based esoteric programming language</title>
      <link>http://mypalmike.github.io/posts/skastic-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 22:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mypalmike.github.io/posts/skastic-intro/</guid>
      <description>This .png file is source code.    I came across a post on slashdot recently about an esoteric programming language based on ASCII art. (https://developers.slashdot.org/story/17/08/13/2033239/new-asciidots-programming-language-uses-ascii-art-and-python). It&#39;s pretty novel and interesting, and in the comments section, people mentioned some related languages with similar characteristics which can be found on esolangs.org. I was intrigued by some other languages which use lines to show control or data flow, some of which are found in a list of two-dimensional languages https://esolangs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>